expertblogz.com 2019-06-10

# Expert's BLOG | Privacy Policy & Disclaimer

This website is an online portal community where different users can post the content and we show aggregate blogs, There is no adult or any 18+ related content on the website. All trademarks, trade names, service marks, copyrighted work, logos referenced herein belong to their respective owners/companies.

Please read and understand clearly that We do not host any of the images/videos here nor we have uploaded any, they have added by respective users. We only facilitate service for blog writing. if there are some images or videos they directly come from third party video hosting sites such as Dailymotion, YouTube and various other third party video hosting sites. Contact those sites for any video removals. This website is NOT hosting content you see. Therefore, our website is not responsible for the accuracy, compliance, copyright, legality, decency, or any other aspect of the content of other linked sites. If you have any legal issues please contact the appropriate media file owners / host sites. These videos are publicly available and you can contact the appropriate sites for removal. All the videos linked in this website are from licensed distributors. 

If a video/logo/artical are violating copyright and you want us to remove that videos/content or have any Questions/Suggestions/Problems contact us before sending email please read our Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA)

All the media files in this site are used only for sampling purposes. Neither we intentionally distribute any copy righted media files nor are we aware that they are copy righted. expertblogz owns none of the files hosted or published on this site. All the files are taken from free servers which don’t claim any copy rights associated with the files. We have complete control over the site to remove any files which are violating copyrights of an individual or organization. If any of the files are copyrighted please notify us and we promptly remove those files from our site.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Expert's Blog collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Expert's Blog.co website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Expert's Blog.

**Personal identification information**

** ** We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Expert's Blog may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

** ** We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Expert's Blog has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, This website makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This website does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, .

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.This website privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
